referralkey.com 2010-04-28

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Your privacy is extremely important to us. Referral Key operates by these principles to protect your privacy.

  1. Your personal information will never be sold to third parties for any marketing purposes  

  2. Your contact information and personal information will never be shared with another member or user without your consent.  

  3. We will only share your personal information with third parties to provide specific services. For example, we utilize credit card processing companies to bill Gold Key members for monthly membership fees. These third party users do not store or retain any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and must adhere to strict confidentiality and privacy agreements which limit the use of such personal information.  

  4. We will not select other companies to send you information about their services and products.  

  5. You may cancel your membership or participation as a referral associate at any time. If you cancel your Referral Key membership or participation as a referral associate, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from public viewing.   

  6. We will use all industry protocols and technology to secure any sensitive information you provide.  

  7. To ensure that the personal information you provide to Referral Key is accurate and current, you may review and update your personal information at any time.  

  8. The Referral Key website is a vehicle by which business professionals people seek to provide referrals to one another. With our consent, all the personal and business information you enter onto the Referral Key website and choose to be displayed may be viewable by members and the general public.  

  9. By becoming a member of Referral Key and or by agreeing to exchange referrals with members, we may email you announcements and promotional information. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, please send to requests to [info@referralkey.com](mailto:info@referralkey.com).  

  10. Referral Key may disclose general information about its members and their referral associates (demographics, business industry, job title, etc) but not individual personal information to third parties without the members or their referral associates permission.  

  11. Like many websites, Referral Key uses cookies and similar software to collect data about users to track their movements around the website and in order to help users to automatically and seamlessly sign in on subsequent visits to the site.  

  12. You have the option to manually enter, upload or import information about your contacts into the private “My Contacts” section of our website. Data entered in the My Contacts section will only be viewable by you and will not be seen by others in the Referral Key network without your permission. The My Contacts section data is covered by all the terms of this privacy policy.  

  13. You MUST be 18 years to join Referral Key.  

  14. There is a possibility that we may need to disclose your personal information when required by law. We shall only disclose such information when we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order or other legal proceeding.  

  15. If at any time you have any questions or comments about this privacy policy, please notify us via email at [info@referralkey.com](mailto:info@referralkey.com) or contact us at: 

> Referral Key, Inc.  
>  20 Park Plaza, #448  
>  Boston, MA 02492

Close
